Hello?
Hey, it's me. Um…
Do you have a few minutes to chat?
Mmm. Yeah, course. Everything good?
Um…
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
Huh?
I… Wha…
What are you trying to…
Out of nowhere? Uh…
Forgive me.
It's just not gonna work out.
Hold on a minute.
How do you know it won't?
What's going on?
Look.
It's because…
we live in two different worlds.
We can't even meet in public
because we're afraid of being seen.
Well, forget that.
Let's meet up right now, okay?
No, I…
I can't do this anymore. I'm sorry.
To be completely honest,
it really hurt me
when you said those things on TV
without asking me.
Huh?
How come you didn't mention this before?
If that's how you felt,
why didn't you tell me?
- Hmm.
Well, okay.
I see.
I understand what you're saying.
I'm sorry. I got overexcited, I guess.
I get it now.
Let's break up.
Goodbye.
- Oh boy, this is not gonna be fun.
- Agreed.
- What do you think will happen?
- This is bad.
- What do we do about the show?
- Morning.
- It's really…
- Morning, Yumi.
- Good morning.
- Hey, morning. Hmm.
RUMOURED SEX THERAPIST'S FAMILY SCANDAL
There you are.
Since the article was published,
we've been getting messages from the media
requesting to interview students
regarding your lectures.
Yes, I know.
All I can say is,
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
I've told Professor Kurusu
not to have you in for lectures anymore.
I understand.
Excuse me.
Why are you so fascinated with sex?
Isn't it too much for you to handle?
Well, it is quite fascinating.
His father, a renowned surgeon,
removed his mother's lover's "bleep"
with a scalpel.
Aah!
Ugh.
But obviously, nothing in this story
directly involves Ichinose.
Still, that won't matter
to our audience at all.
You know that?
Yeah.
You brought us a lot
of negative attention.
I apologize for that again.
It was a mistake
to announce a relationship like that.
It wasn't just a mistake.
You went 100% off script
when we were live!
Yeah. So no, it's not a mistake.
I don't know, Yumi,
I thought you were smarter than that.
Ah. Look, I think it's in
the best interest of both parties, Yumi,
that you take a break
from appearing on the show
until people forget this whole thing.
I'd go check on Ichito.
See how he's doing.
I think he'd like that.
- He wouldn't.
- Hmm.
'Cause…
we're not together anymore, so…
Hm?
Hmm.
Hmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Uh…
Uh, I see.
SHIMOTORI CLINIC
Yes. No, I understand.
Take care of yourself.
Doctor,
your 4:30 patient just called
and cancelled their appointment as well.
Oh. Okay.
Thank you, Marin.
I have to tell you something. I respect
the fact you're doing this face-to-face.
You've been such a mentor.
Well, if not nursing,
what do you wanna do?
Oh! Haven't given much thought, huh? Hmm.
Listen to me, Yuta.
When you told me
you wanted out of the hospital
because you were so exhausted
from the long hours,
do you know why I recommended
putting you with Dr. Shimotori?
The reason?
It wasn't because I thought
it would be easier for you.
You have an energy about you, Yuta.
You brighten up rooms you're in.
You don't force your presence onto people,
so that's a good quality to have.
The psychiatric field needs that.
Honestly,
I thought Dr. Shimotori needed you
more than you needed him.
Mmm.
But
I guess none of it matters
after that article, huh?
If that's what you want, so be it.
I won't stop you again. Not personally.
Come in.
Hmm.
I'm sorry. I might've told her
you wanted to quit.
Bleugh.
This is for you.
Thanks.
Man, I'm so jealous of the students.
No, try it!
- They're so happy and full of hope.
- Do it, come on!
Well, that's what I say.
But I don't know them.
I'm sure they have their own problems.
So that's it, huh?
I guess this isn't our big break!
So many cancellations!
It's not fair. His parents' stuff
has nothing to do with him.
It's not like he takes
after his dad, right?
Oh, is that funny to you?
I've done therapy with him
in the past, you know?
Oh, it's true.
It was, uh, my girlfriend and I.
Whenever we were done, you know,
she'd ask me to go and take a shower.
I just thought she wanted me
to get cleaned up.
But, I don't know, it was odd.
So, once, I took a peek.
And she was doing it alone.
Man, it felt so awful!
It…
It was like I wasn't enough
to satisfy her, you know?
So I went to see him about it.
He listened and took me very seriously.
What my needs and desires were,
how I should approach her.
He encouraged me
to open up to her and discuss it.
So, that's exactly what I did.
And, in the end, talking was key.
'Cause even though we're both women,
we found out that
what works for one of us
doesn't necessarily work for the other.
And it was an important lesson
for us both.
Hold on just a second.
Hmm?
You came here to stop me, right?
Well, I've made up my mind.
Sorry, but I have.
Thank you for the drink.
Shouldn't have told him all that.
FUMI-NO-MIYAKO URBAN LANDSCAPE AWARD
Shirohebi Slope, Sendagi, Bunkyo Ward.
20 steps on the upper level.
Ten steps on the middle level.
BS STAIRWAY PRAISE
And eight steps on the lower level.
This gorgeous set of stairs also
doubles as a route for a nearby school.
The upper level
has elegant white handrails,
and a freshly commissioned
coat of paint.
- From just last month.
- Oh.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Ah. The last section, where
you mention the fresh coat of paint,
could you give us a little…
more emotion and passion?
Yes. I'm sorry.
- Great, let's take it back from the top.
- Okay.
Hey. I see someone's
putting in some overtime.
- Looks like I'm not alone.
- Heading home?
- Yeah. Doing the same?
- Mmm.
I knew it would be a long one,
so I took my car.
- You want a lift?
- Oh…
Thank you, but you can
just drop me off at a station, please.
It's fine, I'll take you home.
No.
There could still be reporters there.
If they get pics of us,
it'll cause more problems,
and you don't need that, Shun.
Getting caught one more time
isn't gonna change much.
And honestly,
I don't really care
if they get pictures of us.
Maybe we just hit the beach?
Be spontaneous?
Huh? What?
I heard you're going
through a breakup right now, so…
Wait…
What's that have to do with the beach?
Oh, you know you want to.
Trust me, it'll be fun.
Not tonight.
Let's go eat some crabs!
Let's go with a smile!
I don't think so.
Let's go clear our minds!
Just take me to the station, please.
Okay, uh…
It's too bad.
Well, cheer up.
You're all good.
You're too tough
to let something like this ruin you.
I'm sorry.
Yes!
So, this is what
it feels like sitting here.
Just by changing where you sit,
the whole impression
of the room changes with it.
So, what seems to be the problem?
I can't get it up.
I…
never told my girlfriend
that I was working here.
It got awkward when she found out.
It was fine, we managed
to patch things up, but…
she was curious if the job
made me re-evaluate our sex life.
So, that got in my head and suddenly,
I couldn't stop re-evaluating.
Oh.
Mm.
- Just a second.
- Huh? What's wrong?
Just…
What?
- Gimme a, uh…
- Huh? Huh?
Ah.
No…
The more I tried to push
those thoughts away and act normal,
the more awkward it got.
Suddenly, out of nowhere,
I was worried about getting it up.
And things just spiralled from there.
When you'd say, "When it comes to sex,
no one is sure about anything,"
I thought it was a load of bull.
Now, I believe it wholeheartedly.
I never in a million years
thought I'd be someone
who had trouble getting an erection.
Hmm.
What are you doing over there?
Oh.
Ah, perfect, there!
What do you say
to a little field trip, huh?
Drawing can be pretty relaxing, huh?
Um…
What exactly is this for?
You've heard of
the autonomic nervous system, right?
Huh? Oh, course.
The sympathetic nervous system
is activated
when someone gets nervous or excited,
and the parasympathetic nervous system
is triggered when you're relaxed.
- Isn't that it?
- Exactly, very good.
However, an erection is a function
of the parasympathetic nervous system.
Huh?
So, basically, you get an erection
not because you're excited,
but 'cause you're relaxed.
Huh.
So, the real reason
you're unable to get an erection
has nothing to do with excitement.
It's a common misconception.
It happens because we become nervous,
and our sympathetic system is dominant.
In other words,
it's because you're trying too hard.
Wow, okay, so…
can I learn to control that at all?
I think the answer is
to engage in relaxing foreplay.
And how exactly does that work?
Most guys try too hard. They think
it needs to be like in porn videos.
And that triggers their sympathetic
nervous system to take over.
But you don't know how
that will affect the woman,
and that can also
be an issue moving forward.
The true purpose of foreplay
is to help one another relax.
And in doing that,
you'll find that your bodies
naturally prepare themselves for sex.
Okay, sure, but how is that done?
Here's a good one.
You start by sitting
and facing your partner,
and you massage one another's backs.
Look. Just like this.
What exactly am I looking at?
- It's foreplay! What do you think?
- Hmm?
- Oh.
- This is the face.
See? Just holding each other intimately.
- You'll feel your partner relax.
- Oh. It's a mermaid! A mermaid, right?
- I swear, Yuta, you're hilarious.
- Huh?
Now, look closely. You see how it works?
Wha… No, no, no, no, no.
I don't understand this at all.
And frankly, you should stop using
your silly kid drawings in your practice.
It just confuses people.
Hey, I'm back!
Welcome, welcome.
- Okay, then, let me see it.
- Oh.
Hey, Yuta.
You couldn't organize
the client files, could you?
Oh, also, it might be time
to get the humidifiers going.
No real rush, though.
Huh?
Huh? What is it?
Uh, can you get back to work?
Oh, yeah. I'll handle it.
- Good.
- Organize the files and--
Yeah, just do it.
Thank you!
I hope…
that one day…
you and I can really connect, you know?
That we…
can be together physically.
Yes.
No problem, we'll cancel it.
Please take care, thank you.
- Hello, there.
- I know you don't have an appointment.
No, but I was hoping
you could squeeze me in.
No offense,
but it doesn't seem to be too busy today.
That okay?
You've got nerve,
coming here after what you did.
I was just doing my job. I'm a reporter.
Oh,
there you are, doctor.
Hello, there.
Marin, I got it. Thank you.
Humans are strange creatures, aren't they?
You'd think, after experiencing
such a gruesome incident,
you would want to keep yourself far away
from anything related to what happened.
But you're an odd guy.
Not only did you not avoid sex,
you turned it into a career.
Tell me,
how have things been going with your wife?
- Have you tried talking…
- One second. Hold on.
I would imagine something like that
might awaken something deep inside,
some kind of sexual perversion, maybe?
That could explain why you took a job
where you can dig deep
into strangers' sex lives, huh?
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
- Yuta, don't.
- Yeah, Yuta, don't.
I mean, we're sorta in the same industry.
Me and both of you.
You guys know it's true.
Huh?
You expose people's issues
and profit off them, right?
You know that's a load of bull!
You have no idea the good he's done
for clients who walk through these doors.
- I'm lucky to get a front-row seat.
- Yuta, I don't need--
I'm not gonna listen to him lie!
There was a time
when I thought the same as you.
Thought that sex therapy
was just a load of absolute nonsense.
So I was embarrassed.
I didn't tell anyone I worked here,
not even my girlfriend.
But you have no idea how many people
are suffering these problems in silence
because they're ashamed.
It's so important
to have someone who cares
and is willing to listen to you
without judging or laughing in your face.
- Oh, I see--
- Even someone who screwed him over!
- Yuta, sit down.
- And he's still willing to help you!
Yuta, I said that's enough!
You're in front of a patient.
You need to be professional.
I'm sorry.
- My apologies.
- No, don't worry.
Please, sit down.
That was sick!
Oh, please, no, don't.
"I'm not gonna listen to him lie!"
Don't, I'm not in the mood.
I never asked you.
Why did you choose nursing, Yuta?
Why do you suddenly care?
What, I'm not allowed to be curious?
I was just wondering,
with your family's history and all.
Well, when I was young,
I really wanted
to play professional soccer.
Oh, wow!
But, then, I got a serious injury
in high school and had to quit.
- I… had surgery at my family's hospital--
- Oh, there!
- What?
- That's when you fell in love with being--
No, stop, I'm trying to tell you.
Well, to be fair, that's sort of it.
Um, my older brother
was always the golden child,
so obviously, he inherited everything.
I wasn't good at studying
or any of that stuff.
I was the black sheep
of the family, for sure.
So, when I couldn't even play soccer,
they really stopped caring.
You know who did care, though?
Who cheered me on?
It was my nurse.
That's when I first thought
that nurses were pretty cool.
I realized that,
you know, maybe I couldn't be a doctor,
but I could be a nurse.
My parents would like that.
But, of course, they told me
that having a nurse
in a family of doctors was a disgrace.
I shouldn't have been shocked.
Oh, that's so harsh.
It was actually freeing,
'cause I realized I didn't care.
So I pursued it anyway.
And so, yeah. That was that.
Now, I'm a nurse.
Interesting.
But it wasn't all sunshine and
rainbows. I was still all over the place.
I had zero confidence at all.
But that's not the case anymore.
Oh. I'm sorry, I gotta go, okay?
Huh? Everything okay?
Yeah.
I made up my mind.
I'm gonna call my brother.
Tell him I'm gonna continue
working for Dr. Shimotori.
- Mmm!
- This is where I belong.
Oh. I'm glad.
'Cause I know he needs me!
Mm-hm.
Good luck!
- You got this!
- Shh-shh.
I think I said something awful to him.
I told him, "One day…
I hope that we can really connect,
and maybe be together physically."
I…
was being so insensitive
to something that's obviously
still really hard for him.
I have to assume that he
found out that the article
was being published,
and that's why he dumped me.
That's not what he said,
but I think he was protecting me from it.
Ugh, I'm sorry, this is annoying now.
I can't hear any more
"He obviously thought this and that,"
or "I guess I just don't deserve this."
Oh, I'm not telling you this
as your shrink,
but just as a personal opinion.
Okay?
Being considerate is beautiful and all,
but if you truly love someone,
you gotta accept that
you're likely gonna get hurt,
or maybe you'll be the one hurting them.
If you're both too afraid,
you'll never be able to move forward.
What happened that day
has to do with you too.
"September 23rd, 17 years ago."
"At a small shrine in Kanagawa Prefecture,
the annual lantern festival
was being held."
- Hello, welcome!
- Hi! Good morning!
Thank you very much!
Thanks a lot!
Hello, there.
I want you to tell me.
About the day of the festival.
Tell me what happened to you.
You owe me that.
Just read the article if you wanna know.
No, I wanna hear it from you, Ichito.
Because I waited.
Till the end of the festival.
And you never told me the reason.
Then you disappeared
and transferred schools,
and I never got an answer.
It's haunted me for a long time.
Seriously, I'm still wondering
why you did it.
Come on, it's been 17 years.
Please, I…
need to know why, once and for all.
I also went…
to the shrine that day.
I was there.
I got a…
DAD
…call from my father.
What's up, Dad?
My father's voice
sounded scared and desperate.
Huh?
He told me my mother had disappeared,
and that I needed to get home right away.
He told me
we were gonna go look for my mom.
But I could tell that he already knew
where she was.
Okay, let's go.
Whose house is this?
Are we allowed to just go in?
Ichito.
I want you to look closely.
Stop it.
Don't!
Ah! No, you can't!
Stop!
My mother was always…
so devoted and loving
to our family.
I thought I was so lucky.
I thought we were the perfect family.
The reason I became a sex therapist…
…is 'cause, since that day, I hate sex.
I saw something meant
to bring connection and love…
destroy these people I care for.
When I first discovered
sexology in medical school,
I thought…
"Oh, maybe sex can be treated
logically too. What a relief."
If I could treat it…
with knowledge instead of emotion…
I hoped the disgust inside of me
could eventually fade away.
But no.
It's still in me.
Um…
where are your parents now?
Well, my dad was in prison for a while.
I don't know where he went
when he was released.
And my mom…
I heard she was institutionalized.
You heard?
I haven't seen her since that day.
My dad's family took me in.
And after that…
I just don't know…
…why he had to take it that far.
I'm not…
sure why my mom cheated on my dad.
There's so much I don't understand.
My mom always seemed so happy.
Let's find out.
What?
Let's go find her.
I'll go with you.
If you don't try, you'll never know.
Let's go find your mother, Ichito.